Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and Photographs WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series V: Addendum, 1957-2004
  - Subseries F: General Files, 1957-2004.
    - LaGuardia Community College Chapter: Grievances (I), 1972-1989 (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - LaGuardia Community College Chapter: Grievances (II), 1972-1989 (Box 173, Folder 14)
    - LaGuardia Community College Chapter: Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Leadership Bulletin, 1982 (Box 173, Folder 16)
    - Lectures, 1971-1974 (Box 173, Folder 17)
    - Legal (I), 1970-1981 (Box 173, Folder 18)
    - Legal (II), 1970-1981 (Box 173, Folder 19)
    - Legal, 1999-2000 (Box 173, Folder 20)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Legislation: Federal (I), 1981 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Legislation: Federal (II), 1981 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1982-1983 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1984-1985 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1986 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1989-1990 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Legislation: Federal, 1992-1996 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Legislation: New York City, 1975-1995 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Conference, 1971-1976 (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Conference and United Federation of College Teachers Merger, 1972-1979 (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Conference: Cross Campus Unit, 1971-1972 (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - Legislators Borough Meetings, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - Legislature: CUNY-SUNY Parity, 1976- 1977 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1978-1985 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1986-1991 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1992-1995 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1996 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1997 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1998 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1999 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Lehman College Chapter: Grievances, 1976-1989 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Lehman College Chapter: Newsletter, 1973-1980 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Lehman College Chapter: Self-Study Report on Technology, 1999 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Librarians, 1972-1987 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Mailgrams, 1980-1981 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Manhattan Community College Chapter, 1986-1998 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - Manhattan Education Opportunity Center, 1988-2000 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Manhattan Urban Center Chapter, 1972-1988 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1973-1982 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1984 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1985-1987 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1988-1990 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1991-1992 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1993-1998 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter: Clippings, 1984-1999 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter: Grievances, 1977-1984 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Medical Benefits, 1977 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Membership, 1973-1979 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Membership (I), 1982 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Membership (II), 1982 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Membership, 1983 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Membership, 1990-1993 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Russell, 1970-1974 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1977 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Municipal Labor Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Municipal Labor Committee, 1983-1992 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Municipal Labor Committee, 1995-2000 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Murphy, Joseph S., 1982-1990 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1973-1999 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: Newsletter, 1979-1992 (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - National Education Association (NEA), 1972-1974 (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - NEA, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - NEA, 1976-1991 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - NEA: American Federation of Teachers (AFT) Merger, 1994 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - NEA: Board of Director, 1974-1976 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - NEA: Convention, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - NEA: Convention, 1976 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - NEA: Executive Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - NEA: Representative Assembly, 1974-1975 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - National Higher Education Staff Association, 1972-1975 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW), 1974 (Box 177, Folder 10)
    - National Testing Network in Writing (NTNW), 1982 (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Negotiations: Non-Classroom Positions, 1972-1973 (Box 177, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, 1974 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, 1975 (Box 177, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, 1976 (Box 177, Folder 16)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, 1977 (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, 1978-1979 (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, Jan 1980-Mar 1980 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, Apr 1980-Aug 1980 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters and Circulars, Sep 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - New York Central Labor Council (NYCLC), 1971-1988 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - New York City Community College: Grievances, 1977-1979 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - New York City Community College: Newsletter, 1973-1980 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - New York City Council, 1972-1978 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - New York City Employees Retirement System (ERS) and Teachers Retirement System (TRS), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - New York City Financial Control Board, 1979-1986 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Office of the Mayor, 1974-1993 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - New York City Technical College (NYCTC) Chapter, 1980-1984 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - NYCTC Chapter, 1985-1990 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - NYCTC Chapter, 1991-1999 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - NYCTC Chapter: Correspondence, 1980-1999 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - NYCTC Chapter: Future Report, 1999-2000 (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - NYCTC Chapter: Grievances, 1980-1982 (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - NYCTC Chapter: Newsletter, 1980 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - New York State Assembly: Committee on Labor, 1975-1976 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - New York State Board of Regents, 1996-1999 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - New York State Comptroller, 1997-1998 (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - New York State Division of Human Right, 1976-1983 (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - New York State Education Department, 1972-1977 (Box 178, Folder 22)
    - New York State Emergency Financial Control Board, 1977 (Box 178, Folder 23)
    - New York State Senate, 1974-1979 (Box 178, Folder 24)
    - New York State United Teacher (NYSUT), 1980-1984 (Box 178, Folder 25)
    - NYSUT, 1985-1990 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - NYSUT: Ad Hoc Committee for Higher Education, 1974 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - NYSUT: Benefits, 1997-1999 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1980-1986 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors' Retreat, 1999 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - NYSUT: College and University Council, 1976-1978 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - NYSUT: Committee of 100, 1976 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - NYSUT: Committee of 100, 1996-1998 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - NYSUT: Committee on Political Education (COPE), 1986-1990 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - NYSUT: DeLeonardis, Vito, 1974-1980 (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - NYSUT: Executive Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - NYSUT: Hobart, Thomas, 1974-1978 (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - NYSUT: Koenig, Pat, 1978 (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - NYSUT: Legislative Updates, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - NYSUT: Legislative Updates, 1996-1999 (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - NYSUT: Long Term Care Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - NYSUT: Lubin, Alan-Testimony, 1997 (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - NYSUT: Membership Services, 1977-1980 (Box 179, Folder 19)
    - NYSUT: Political Action Committee (PAC), 1995-2000 (Box 179, Folder 20)
    - NYSUT: Representative Assembly, 1993-2000 (Box 179, Folder 21)
    - NYSUT: Sanders, Dan, 1974-1976 (Box 179, Folder 22)
    - NYSUT: Skuse, Ray, 1977-1978 (Box 179, Folder 23)
    - NYSUT: Streiff, Dean, 1978 (Box 179, Folder 24)
    - New York Times, 1971-1976 (Box 179, Folder 25)
    - New York Trade Union Women's Conference, 1973 (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - New York University, 1972-1974 (Box 179, Folder 27)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1981-1985 (Box 179, Folder 28)
    - OSHA, 1986-1990 (Box 179, Folder 29)
    - Office of Academic Affairs, 1980-1989 (Box 179, Folder 30)
    - Office of Academic Affairs (I), 1990-1995 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Office of Academic Affairs (II), 1990-1995 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Oldham, Pat, Feb 1983 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Open Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Panken, Irving (I), 1980-1981 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Panken, Irving (II), 1980-1981 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Panken, Irving, 1982 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Parikh, Rohit, 1981-1982 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - Part-Time Personnel and Adjuncts, 1980-1984 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Part-Time Personnel and Adjuncts, 1985-1986 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Part-Time Personnel and Adjuncts, 1987-1991 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Part-Time Personnel and Adjuncts: Clippings, 1974-1995 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Payless Furlough, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Pension Committee, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - Pension Plan (I), 1989-1995 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Pension Plan (II), 1989-1995 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Personnel Practices, 1974-1976 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1982 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1983 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1984 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1985-1986 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 1987-1989 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Polishook, Irwin, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Polish Solidarity Movement, 1981-1982 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Political Clubs (Democrat and Republican), 1977 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York, 1974 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases, 1975-1978 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Primary Election Bulletin, 1976 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - Professional Staff Congress (PSC): A. Philip Randolph Institute Conference, 1981 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - PSC: Audit, 1973-1992 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - PSC: Contract (I), 1972-1987 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - PSC: Contract (II), 1972-1987 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - PSC: Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - PSC: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - PSC: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - PSC: Hotline, 1995-2000 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - PSC: Human Rights Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - PSC: Legislative Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - PSC: Legislative Council, 1972-1975 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - PSC: Legislative Council, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - PSC: Legislative Council, 1978-1989 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - PSC: Legislative Council, 1995-1996 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    - PSC: Membership, 1986-2000 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    - PSC: New Caucus, 1996-1999 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    - PSC: Officer Speeches, 1973-1976 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    - PSC: Officer Speeches, 1995-1996 (Box 182, Folder 10)
    - PSC: Pension Committee, 1973-1986 (Box 182, Folder 11)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1971-1975 (Box 182, Folder 12)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 13)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1978-1980 (Box 182, Folder 14)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 15)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1982-1985 (Box 182, Folder 16)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1986-1989 (Box 182, Folder 17)
    - PSC: Personnel, 1990-1995 (Box 182, Folder 18)
    - PSC: Records Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - PSC: Strike Committee, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - PSC: Welfare Fund, 1993-1999 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - PSC: Women's Conference, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Professional Staff Union (PSU), 1973-1979 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - PSU, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - PSU, 1983-1988 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - PSU, 1989-1994 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Professional Unions, 1975-1991 (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Protest/Public Demonstration, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 10)
    - Public Disclosure Law (I), 1972-1980 (Box 183, Folder 11)
    - Public Disclosure Law (II), 1972-1980 (Box 183, Folder 12)
    - Public Employees Federation (PEF), 1976-1993 (Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Public Employment Relations Board (PERB), 1972-1981 (Box 183, Folder 14)
    - PERB: Certification and Unit Determination, 1967-1972 (Box 183, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, 1972-1974 (Box 183, Folder 16)
    - Public Relations, 1990-1994 (Box 183, Folder 17)
    - Puerto Rican Council on Higher Education, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 18)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1979-1984 (Box 183, Folder 19)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1985 (Box 183, Folder 20)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1986 (Box 183, Folder 21)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 183, Folder 22)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1989-1999 (Box 183, Folder 23)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter: Grievances, 1977-1988 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1983-1984 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1985-1986 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1989-1993 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1994-1996 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1997-1999 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Queens College Chapter: Grievances, 1981-1983 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Queens College Chapter: Labor Resource Center, 1996-1999 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Queens College Chapter: Newsletter, 1974-1980 (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Queens College Chapter: Publicity, 1988-1998 (Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Queens College Law School Chapter, 1989-1995 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Queens College Law School Chapter, 1998-2000 (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Queens Education Opportunity Center, 1999 (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Rebate, 1982 (Box 184, Folder 17)
    - Registrars Chapter, 1973-1997 (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - Remedial Education-Search for Education Evaluation and Knowledge (SEEK) Program, 1980-1996 (Box 184, Folder 19)
    - Remediation, 1998-1999 (Box 184, Folder 20)
    - Research Assistants, 1992-1995 (Box 184, Folder 21)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 22)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1981-1982 (Box 184, Folder 23)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1983 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1984 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1985 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1986 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1987-1988 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1989-1991 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1992 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1993-1994 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1995 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York, 1996-1999 (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York: Contract (I), 1979-1991 (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York (II), 1979-1991 (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York: Project Directors Guide, 1987 (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York: Grievances, 1984-1988 (Box 185, Folder 14)
    - Research Foundation of the City University of New York: Negotiations, 1980-1988 (Box 185, Folder 15)
    - Residency Law, 1978 (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - Resolutions, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1973-1975 (Box 185, Folder 18)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1976-1979 (Box 185, Folder 19)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1980-1984 (Box 185, Folder 20)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1987-2000 (Box 185, Folder 21)
    - Retirees Chapter: Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 185, Folder 22)
    - Retirement, 1976-1986 (Box 185, Folder 23)
    - Retirement/Pensions, 1977-1993 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Retrenchment, 1975-1977 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Retrenchment, 1981-1983 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Retrenchment, 1984-1996 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Retrenchment: American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1979-1982 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Reynolds, Ann-CUNY Chancellor, 1992-1994 (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Richmond College: Newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Romain, Dr. Charles B., 1982 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Safety Committee, 1991-1997 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Salaries (I), 1957-1993 (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Salaries (II), 1957-1993 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Salute to Scholars, 1982 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Sand, John E., 1975-1976 (Box 186, Folder 13)
    - Scholars in Transition, 1983 (Box 186, Folder 14)
    - Secretarial Science, 1982 (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Select Faculty Committee, 1975-1994 (Box 186, Folder 16)
    - Self-Help Fair, 1982 (Box 186, Folder 17)
    - Settlement Agreements, 1973-1978 (Box 186, Folder 18)
    - Settlement Agreements, 1979-1984 (Box 186, Folder 19)
    - Sexual Harassment (I), 1980-1996 (Box 186, Folder 20)
    - Sexual Harassment (II), 1980-1996 (Box 186, Folder 21)
    - Sims, Carol, 1978-1981 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Social Democrats, 1973 (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Solicitations, 1990-1995 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Speeches, 1972-1976 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Staff Contracts, 1979-1989 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University, 1974 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Starling, Dr. Marion, 1976-1982 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Statement of Principals, 1996 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Statements, 1976-1981 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - State Tuition assistance Program (STAP) Guidelines, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Staten Island Community College: Newsletter, 1973-1975 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - State University of New York (SUNY), 1970-1973 (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - SUNY, 1981 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - SUNY, 1985-1986 (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - SUNY, 1987-1992 (Box 187, Folder 15)
    - SUNY, 1993-1997 (Box 187, Folder 16)
    - SUNY: Clippings, 1976-1986 (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - SUNY: Constitution and Bylaws, 1972 (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - Strikes, 1975-1990 (Box 187, Folder 19)
    - Student Demonstrations, 1991-1999 (Box 187, Folder 20)
    - Student Evaluation of Faculty, 1972-1974 (Box 187, Folder 21)
    - Student Life Personnel Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 187, Folder 22)
    - Students, 1972-1996 (Box 187, Folder 23)
    - Student Voter Registration, 1976 (Box 187, Folder 24)
    - Summer Hours, 1975-1978 (Box 187, Folder 25)
    - Tarrytown Conference, 1975-1979 (Box 187, Folder 26)
    - Task Force on Higher Education, 1975-1978 (Box 187, Folder 27)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1982 (Box 187, Folder 28)
    - Tax Deferred Annuity, 1974-1998 (Box 187, Folder 29)
    - Teacher Education, 1972-1973 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Teacher Education, 1977 (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Teacher Education, 1986-1988 (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Teacher Insurance and Annuity Association, 1996-1999 (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Teacher Recruitment: Internship Project, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Teacher Recruitment: Internship Project, 1987 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Teacher Retirement System, 1973-1995 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Telecourses, 1982 (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Temporary Commission on the Future of Post Secondary Education, 1977 (Box 188, Folder 9)
    - Tenure, 1973-1976 (Box 188, Folder 10)
    - Tilden Financial Corporation: Insurance, 1969 (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - Transit Strike, 1980-1999 (Box 188, Folder 12)
    - Trent, Richard, 1978 (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - Tuition, 1972-1979 (Box 188, Folder 14)
    - Tuition Assistance Program (TAP), 1981 (Box 188, Folder 15)
    - Tuition Tax Credit Bills, 1978-1981 (Box 188, Folder 16)
    - Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1975-1976 (Box 188, Folder 17)
    - United Federation of Teachers (UFT), undated (Box 188, Folder 18)
    - UFT: Correspondence, 1973-1989 (Box 188, Folder 19)
    - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare: Office of Civil Rights, 1975 (Box 188, Folder 20)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1974 (Box 188, Folder 21)
    - United States Department of State, 1978 (Box 188, Folder 22)
    - United University Professions (UUP), 1975-1992 (Box 188, Folder 23)
    - UUP, 1994-1999 (Box 188, Folder 24)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1971-1979 (Box 188, Folder 25)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1980-1983 (Box 188, Folder 26)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1984-1985 (Box 188, Folder 27)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1986-1988 (Box 188, Folder 28)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1990-1994 (Box 188, Folder 29)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1995 (Box 188, Folder 30)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1996-1997 (Box 188, Folder 31)
    - University Faculty Senate, 1998-2000 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - University Student Senate, 1971-1985 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Urban Higher Education Research Forum, 1982 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Vladeck, Judith, 1993-1994 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - University Faculty Senateladeck, Stephen, 1972-1980 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Voorhees Technical Institute, 1973-1985 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Washington Federation of Teachers, 1998 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Water Conservation Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Website, 1997 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Weinberg, Beryl, 1976-1981 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Welfare Fund, 1972-1979 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Welfare Fund, 1980-1983 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Welfare Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Welfare Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Welfare Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Welfare Fund, 1990-1993 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Welfare Fund, 1990-1999 (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - Welfare Fund Newsletter, 1990-1993 (Box 189, Folder 18)
    - Welfare: Trustees Benefits, 1982 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1975-1977 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1978-1979 (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1980-1981 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Harold (PSC Vice President), 1982-1989 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Winter, Joseph, 1982 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Women's Studies, 1982 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Workload, 1971-1981 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Workload, 1982-1983 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1975 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Yellowitz, Irwin, 1984-1989 (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - York College Chapter, 1972-1984 (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - York College Chapter, 1985-1992 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - York College Chapter, 1993-1994 (Box 190, Folder 14)